I'm glad you're here.
If you think you might miss even one job
a month over a missed call, this is for you.
If you think your Google profile could
better represent you, this is for you.
If you'd like to have more
five-star reviews, this is for you.
If you want more qualified
customers, definitely for you.
If you're booked up for two years and
have more customers than you can shake
a stick at, probably not a good fit.
I'm Tony Case, and I built BTTY.
I named her Betty because she serves
as my virtual assistant.
I built her for me because I was drowning
in busywork, and I couldn't keep up.
She changed my life, and
now I can't stop building.
If you'd like to be better today
than yesterday, Betty is for you.
Schedule a call, and I'll
introduce you in person.